NICOLE NAM

Front End Developer

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SASS, REACT, jQuery, Bootstrap, Git, Responsive Design,

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Possessing a strong ability implement mockups and understanding of great user experience, as well as ability to communicate effectively in a team setting. Will utilize experience as a highly organized banquet cook and proven ability to work under pressure to contribute to company's goals and needs.

GET IN TOUCH

Mobile: 647-404-9660 Email: nicolenam.work@gmail.com Portfolio: nicolenam.com

WORK HISTORY

Banquet Cook

Ritz Carlton Hotel -Toronto | Nov. 2016 to Dec. 2019

- Developed, strong organizational, and time management skills in order to boost productivity under pressure.
- Created, and prepared new and enticing menu items for the VIP Lounge quests.
- Managed allergies with care and professionalism for customers' safety and satisfaction.
- Worked effectively with all team members to promote a positive working environment.
- Nurtured strong work ethic and attention to detail.

Banquet Cook

Four Seasons Hotel-Toronto | Sept. 2015 to Nov. 2016

- Demonstrated strong working knowledge of basic cooking and effective preparation methods.
- Prepared over 400 individual meal portions for banquet functions while maintaining 5 star food quality. Instructed student/kitchen personnel in the proper portion control in preparation and service of food.
- Practiced the ability to handle multiple preparations and tasks simultaneously in an efficient manner.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

RED ACADEMY Web Developer Professional Program Attended Jan. 2020 - March 2020

George Brown College Culinary Management

Attended Jan. 2014- Dec. 2015

Dongguk University Theatre Arts Acting

Attended March 2005 - Aug. 2010